Tony Schwartz Collection
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Series 4. Subject Files, 1912–2005, 15.2 linear feet
  - Smoking, circa 1960–2005
    - Air travel, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 191/2)
    - Antismoking campaigns (non-Schwartz), circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 191/3-4)
    - Business and career costs, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 191/5)
    - Dr. William Cahan, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 191/6)
    - Cancer, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 191/7)
    - Celebrity illness and death, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 191/8)
    - Cigarette ad examples, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 191/9)
    - Cipollone tobacco liability case, circa 1990–2005 (Box-folder 191/10)
    - Costs of smoking, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/1)
    - Demographics, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/2)
    - Dresner-Sykes survey, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/3)
    - K.H. Ginzel research, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/4)
    - Health effects, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/5)
    - Illustrations, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/6)
    - Legislation, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/7)
    - Litigation, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/8)
    - Merchants of Death, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/9)
    - New York City, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 192/10-11)
    - New York City and state smoking restriction proposals, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 193/1-2)
    - Overseas marketing, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 193/3)
    - Philip Morris annual report, 1985 (Box-folder 193/4)
    - Philip Morris Magazine, 1986–1989 (Box-folder 193/5)
    - Bill of Rights 200th anniversary brochure from Philip Morris Companies and the National Archives, circa 1991 (Box-folder 230/12)
      Brochure, 16x13 1/2 inches, 4 pages, promoting the 200th anniversary of the U.S. Bill of Rights.
    - Politics, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 193/6)
    - Public attitudes, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 193/7)
    - Quitting smoking, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 193/8)
    - Secondhand smoke (passive smoking), circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 193/9)
    - Smokefree environments, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 193/10)
    - Smokefree workplace, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 194/1-2)
    - Smokeless cigarettes, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 194/3)
    - Smokeless tobacco, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 194/4)
    - Smoking and Health Reporter, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 194/5)
    - Smoking and tobacco (general), circa 1960–2005, (4 folders) (Box 194-195, Box 194, Box 195)
    - Sports and athlete sponsorship, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 195/5)
    - Tisch controversy, 1985–1995 (Box-folder 195/6)
    - Tobacco industry executives, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 195/7)
    - Tobacco sponsorship of arts, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 195/8)
    - Transportation, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 195/9)
    - Bonnie Vierthaler, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 195/10)
    - World Health Organization, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 195/11)
    - Worldwatch Institute, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 195/12)
    - Youth, circa 1960–2005 (Box-folder 195/13)
Transferred Materials
The bulk of the films and videotapes included in the collection were transferred to the Moving Image Section of the Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress, in 2007; a second installment was transferred in 2010. For details, see http://www.loc.gov/rr/mopic/mphours.html.